[{"answer": "It's a big night for Mitt Romney.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "What's your overview?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "Well, look.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "So how significant is Romney's position right now?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting because I don't think Newt Gingrich could decide who he was or what he was.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "What went wrong with Gingrich this week, do you think?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I'm a Buffalo Bills fan.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Wolf?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Gloria?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "And John, I know your allegiance.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "All right?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I'm not surprised at all.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Are you surprised that he's now beginning to beat his chest a bit?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Well, it sure looks like it.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "He's going to throw the kitchen sink at him, isn't he?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Now, Piers.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Are you going to stop baring your teeth in more places?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "I thought it was fantastic.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Have you had a word with him?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I think for Mitt it's just to continue to put himself out there, continue to show that he's got a plan to get America moving forward.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What is the big challenge for Mitt Romney, do you think?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, it's never actually fun to experience that.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "On a human level, how do you as his daughters feel about the bombardment that's coming his way?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "USHMAN: I think part of the process of the primary is to go through this and to go through all the different things you'll see in the general election.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Does that help the Republican Party?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I'm not really sure I'd say that as graceless.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "I mean little bit graceless, wouldn't you think?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "It was a big night for Florida.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Governor, why do you think Mitt Romney has such a thumping victory tonight?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "COTT: I think -- I think what Floridians looked at is they look at he's a business guy.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Suddenly this huge turnaround and it seems to be based around Mitt Romney's better performances in the debates and this relentless negativity of the campaign, which I'll come to in a moment, but why Mitt Romney -- why is he being seen as the savior economically, do you think?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "You know I think when people go to the polls, here's what they say.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Wouldn't it be better for the party to have at least some positivity creeping in here?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "I mean, if Floridians believe that the president is actually turning around the situation, that's good for him, isn't it?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I'm going to -- I'm going to support the Republican nominee.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Are you prepared to back Mr. Romney?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, a lot of wags are saying -- Senator Rubio said that if he wins Florida he wins the nomination.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "He really needs a bit of more this, I think, and momentum will take him to nomination, isn't it?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Look, Catherine, let me ask you.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "I think the big question for a lot of the GOP and Republican establishment so to speak is, can Newt still do damage to Mitt Romney even if Mitt Romney gets the nomination?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, I think there could be a fine line.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Isn't it -- you know, aren't we in the position here where the longer this goes on, it's better for Mitt Romney if he's the one that wins to have this bruising encounter with Gingrich on months on end?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Well, it hasn't disappeared whatsoever.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "The phenomenal Tea Party bursting on to scene and then disappearing almost as fast?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, some watchers, you know, they're speculating that perhaps Rick Santorum is staying in in the hopes of being VP on a Romney ticket.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "You know what do you think of the other two candidates?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "But Newt -- I've been covering Newt Gingrich since the late '80s.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "I wouldn't rule out Newt Gingrich making yet another comeback, would you?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, that's a big if.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "If the economy continues to improve right up to November, he's going to hit a homerun, isn't he?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "I think it all boils down to electability, Piers.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Would you -- would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Has Mitt Romney now made that sort of tipping point move, do you think, to where he's a genuine frontrunner?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Probably Romney.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Who, if you're -- if you're Obama, who do you least want to take on?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, Paul wasn't really competing in Florida.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Santorum and Paul, where are they in this?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Well, if he has -- if he has a lot of delegates in the end and if he has a lot of public support, I mean, the nominee is going to want every single former opponent, you know, to line up behind him.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Does it make him -- no, but does it make him a valuable tool to whoever wants to be the nominee?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Santorum I think tries to stay in it for awhile because there's clearly this bloc of voters who don't want Romney, who are more conservative.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Santorum?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Suddenly I feel like I'm Christina Aguilera on the \"Voice\" or something.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "Barack Obama or Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "I mean, yes, we're talking about -- I can't imagine, it is, you know, we should say this from time to time because we all spend so much time tearing apart the candidates and, you know, in being justly critical of them.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Why would anybody in the modern age really want to be the president given the unbearable workload, stress, the attention?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120131pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "But actually you've got -- as you say, you've got to really want this, haven't you?", "qSentId": 754}]